djmaza.link 2018-09-13

# Privacy Page - DJMaza.Info

### What do we use your information for?

We respect our users privacy and DO NOT COLLECT ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, and only following STANDARD web-analytic information is ever recorded: Analytic to measure traffic and improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We use cookies on our site just to create a better experience for you and to help serve our requirements to improve our services in the future.

### Storage of personal data

If you register to use our online services, to purchase a subscription or call our technical support, you may need to fill out a form asking you to disclose your name and email address. This information will be stored in our databases. This helps to manage user accounts and subscriptions as part of the use of our services. In particular it allows the user to not have to re-enter personal information each time.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy. 

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us
